Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - Stokowski [and Helen] Parkhurst, [1932]
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Stokowski, Sadja
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Stookey, Dr. and Mrs. Byron
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
  - Stookey, Dr. Byron and family
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Stowell, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
  - Strong, Mrs. Corrin (mother, Mrs. Trowbridge)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Strong, Mrs. L. and family (Washington)
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Stuart, ----
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Stuart, Mr. Charles T.
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Studio (Thetford, VT)
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
  - Sullivan St. from Bleeker
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Sutton, Mrs. Ruth
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - [Svetlova?] Swetlowa, Marina, 1969
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Swain, Kathryn
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Swantees, Ethel
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Sweden
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - [Sweden:] Castles in Skane, 1928
    - Negatives (Box FB011)
  - Sweden: Gotland, Visbon
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Sweden: Landscapes, villages, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
    - Negatives (Box FB059)
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Sweden: North Gotland
    - Negatives (Box FB059)
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Sweden: South Gotland
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
  - Sweden: Stockholm
    - Negatives (Box FB059)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Swedish girl 1, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Swedish man 1-5, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB059)
  - Swedish man 6-9, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB060)
  - Swedish man 10-14, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB059)
  - Swedish man 15-21, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB060)
  - Swedish man 22, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Swedish man 23-28, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB060)
  - Swedish man 29-31, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Swedish man 32-36, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Swedish woman 1-6, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Swedish woman 7, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Swedish woman 8, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Taft, Lorado
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
  - Tanaka, Asako
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Taos [NM] (large head of Indian woman, for Phyllis)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Tarasova, Alla as Grushenka in The Brothers Karamazov
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
  - Tarbell, Ida (Bethel, CT)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Tate
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Charles L. (grandchild, Hartford)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Taylor, Derry, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Floyd and Caroline (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Taylor, Susie (daughter of Mrs. E.P. Taylor)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Tea party with Edith, Candace, Phyllis
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Teague, Lucy
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Techin, N.
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Terry, Mrs. George
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Tessin, Emil A. and children
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Tessin, Mary, 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Tetsuka, Mrs. H. (Sharon, Mrs. C. Ford's mother)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Thayer, Mrs. W.E. (daughter Helen, 5 Griffing Blvd., Asheville, NC)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Thetford Type
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Negatives (Box FB203)
  - Thomas, Miss (Lebanese), 1971
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
  - Thompson, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Ralph, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Thompson, Mr. and Mrs. Robert (Burlington)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Thompson, Mrs. Scott, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Thuford, P.O.
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Thurman, Howard, 1963
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Thurston, Mrs. (Thetford), 1934
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Titus
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Tolstoy, Countess Alexandra
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Tomanoff, Prince [Cyril Toumanoff?]
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Torrence, Ridgeley, 1941
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Towner, Mrs. Rutherford (baby)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Trafford, Herbert Mr., 1950
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Trees
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Trees, plan for book, 1840s [?]
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Trentszch, Mrs. P.J. (Dr. B.P. Allen)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Trip west
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Trout, Mrs. Herbert
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - Tucker, Mrs. Beverly (little daughter of)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Tucson, AZ
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Tufts, Mrs. William, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Twins (Londonderry, Washington DC)
    - Negatives (Box FB062)
  - Twitchell, Dr. and Mrs. Coleman (Burlington, Vermont)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Twitchell, M.C. Jr. (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
  - Twitchell, Mrs. M.C. (granddaughter, Burlington, Vermont)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
  - Twitchell-Allen, Dr. Doris and son Rustes
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Ulman, Jean
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
  - Ulman, Mr. (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
  - Underhill, Mrs. H.W. (sons)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
  - Underwood, Mrs. Kenneth, wedding
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Unemployed from my window, NYC
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
  - United States, South
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB141)
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Negatives (Box FB204)
  - United States, Southwest, 1929
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - United States, Southwest, Indian temple
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - United States, West
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Negatives (Box FB203)
  - United States, West, Native Americans
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Upson, Hiram
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Valentine, Miss Myra, 1954
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
  - Van Count, Ens. Albert E.
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
  - Van Laer, Mrs. Eleanor, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
  - Van Loon, Hendrik
    - Negatives (Box 58)
  - Van Sykes, Miss Lillie
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
  - Van Zandt, Roland, 1955
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Van Zandt, Mrs. Roland and group, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Vance, Mrs. and Miss Yale
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
  - Varnum, Mr. Laurent K. (Grand Rapids), 1945
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Vaughan, Christine (mother)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Vaughan, Christine and Charles (Thetford)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Veechi, Dr. Saller, 1969
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Vermont landscapes
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Negatives (Box FB183)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - Negatives (Box FB203)
    - Negatives (Box FB204)
  - Vermont neighbors late in the day
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
  - Vermont, covered bridges
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB203)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Vincent, Helen
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
  - Vining, Elizabeth Gray, 1958; 1963
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB183)
  - Vining, Elizabeth Gray and Gordon Gray, 1957
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB183)
  - Virginia
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB183)
  - Vittoris, Mr. and Mrs. (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Waldman, Alida, hands, 1953
    - Negatives (Box FB112)
  - Waldorf, Mr. H.W., 1954
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Walevitch, [Saveli?]
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Walker, Mr. and Mrs. Charles S.
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Walker, Mrs. Harriet (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Walker, Mrs. Leon
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Walker, Mildred, 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Wall, Berry (group), 1956
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Wall, Jeremiah and daughter, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Wallace, Mrs. D.D.
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Walls, Mr. and Mrs. Jeremiah (youngest daughter)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Walsh, Mr. and Mrs. Richard Jr. (Dick and Tsuta)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Wals, Richard Jr. (John Day Company, 62 W. 45th Street, New York, N.Y. 10036)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Ward, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB145)
  - Warren, Mrs. (horse)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Washburn, Mr. Owen (Oxford, NH)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Washington, DC
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box FB145)
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Washington, DC, cherry trees
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
  - Wasson, Mrs. David A.
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Waterman, Mrs. Marshall (Serena Gow) and son Frank, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Wathen
    See Birch-Wathen items.
  - Wather, Mrs. G.W.
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Watts, Mr. and Mrs. Franklin
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Webster, Mr. and Mrs. Charles H.
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Webster, Mrs. Gertrude
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Webster, Dr. H. and family
    See also DeForest, Mrs. Henry (Webster family).
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Webster, Dr. Jerome, 1940
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Webster, Dr. Jerome (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Webster, Mrs. Jerome
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Webster, Mr. L.T. and Mrs. W. (2 children)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Wehler, Mrs. Louis B. and daughter
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Wehrbane, Mr. Henry
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Wehrbane, Mr. Henry (garden)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Weigl, Mrs. H.J.
    - Negatives (Box FB067)
  - Welch, Mrs. (Hartford), 1935
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Welch, Mrs. Henry K.W. (Hartford, CT)
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Weld, Mr. and Mrs. Edric (Dublin, N.H.)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Weld, Edric and family (Dublin, NH)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
  - Weld, Edric (baby)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Weld, Edric Ammory (Middlebury)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Weld, Gertrude M.
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Wells, Dr. Barbara, 1964
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Wernick, Farah (daughter of Robert Wernick)
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Wernick, Mrs. Robert (baby)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Wertz, Mrs. Frederick L. (25 Mountain Ave., Montclair, NJ)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Weston, Mrs. Edward
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Weston, Mrs. Edward and daughter
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Whalon, Mark
    See Reedy, Father and Mark Whalon.
  - Wheelan, Ed
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Wheelan, Ed (paintings)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Wheeler, Cleora, 1940
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Whitconif, Susan (daughter of Mrs. Louis G. Whitconif)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - White, Dr. Paul, 1961
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - White, Mrs. Frank C. (daughter and son in law)
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - White, Prof. and Mrs. Robert, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - White, Walter
    - Negatives (Box FB068)
  - Whitehead, Mrs. George F. (Brattleboro)
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Whitehead, Helen M. and Robert O. (children of Mrs. George F. Whitehead)
    - Negatives (Box FB146)
  - Whitemore, Mrs. Harris and son
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Whitneck, Jean
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Whulan, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - Wicke, Mr. Carl, 1952
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Wilbur, Mrs. (granddaughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Wilckes, Mrs. Felix, 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Wilcox, ---- (sons of)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - Wilhousky, Peter J., 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Wilkins, Mrs. F.
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - William, Dr. Maurice
    - Negatives (Box 59)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Negatives (Box FB179)
  - William, Mrs. Maurice
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - Williams, Frances, 1956
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Williams, Mary
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Wills, Mrs. William H. (wedding of daughter, Old Bennington)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Wills, Willy
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - Wilson, Mrs. Russel (Cincinnati)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Wiltbank gardens
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 61)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Wiltbank, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Winter scenes
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Wise, Mr. James D.
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - Wistrand, Phillipa (daughter of Mrs. Hugo Wistrand)
    - Negatives (Box FB069)
  - Withey, Miss Martha
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Witte, Mrs. W.J., 1954
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Wolf, Mrs. E.N.
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Wolff, Ruth, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Women with baby carriages
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Wood, E. Allen (Greenwich)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Wood, Mrs. P.J.E. (502 St. Lawrence Ave., Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Woodward, Mrs. H., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Wooley, Mrs. Arthur (garden)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Woolson, ---- (13 year old daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Woolson, Lawrence, 1963
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Woolson, Mrs. Laurina B. (Woodbury Road, R.F.D 2, Springfield, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Worcesters (Thetford)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
  - Workman, Mrs. W.W., 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Wright, Majinol (Berney's mother)
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
  - Yancich, Milan (to Mrs. Mary Sampson)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Yarnall, Mr. Stanley R.
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Yates, Elizabeth, See McGreal, Elizabeth.
  - Yenawine, Dr. Wayne, 1963
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Yepson, Mrs. Marie C.
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Yosemite Valley, Glacier Point, 1929
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Yoshida, word block printing
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
  - Young, Barbara and grandchildren, 1946
    - Negatives (Box 60)
  - Young, Barbara (daughter and granddaughter Sharon)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Young, Barbara and Christopher
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
  - Young, Ella
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
  - Yugoslavia
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB070)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB180)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
    - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Yugoslavia group: Fedja, Ira, Paul, Ivanoff, Irina, Clara E. Sipprell), 1925-1926
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Yugoslavia: Dalmation gardens
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Yugoslavia: Dubrovnik
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Yugoslavia: Mostar and vicinity
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Yugoslavia: Zafret market
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Yung, Miss Wang
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB178)
  - Zaengleim, Billy (son of Mr. W.G. Zaenglein)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Zaenglein, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
  - Zambia River
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - Zecker, Dr. Ilsley and family, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
  - Zecker, Mrs. Ilsley, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB071)
  - Zoraek, William, 1946
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
  - -----, David (Rutland, VT)
    - Negatives (Box FB015)
    - Proof prints (Box 76)
  - ----, Diane, Sept. 1930
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB017)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
  - ----, Louise
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
  - ----, Nicolai (Bishop)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - ----, Paul and friend
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - [Unidentified boy]
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
  - [Unidentified child] Mrs. 's child, 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB128)
  - [Unidentified woman]
    - Negatives (Box FB145)
  - [Unidentified] Little girl on horse (Thetford), 1936
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
  - [Unidentified] Carolyn Davis selections
    - Negatives (Box FB124)
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
  - [Unidentified] Negatives from Lemke's files on Sipprell
    - Negatives (Box FB147)
    - Negatives (Box FB148)
    - Negatives (Box FB149)
    - Negatives (Box FB185)
    - Negatives (Box FB203)
  - [Unidentified] Loose items
    - Negatives (Box FB037)
    - Negatives (Box FB123)
    - Negatives (Box FB189)
    - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - Proof print (Box 79)
  - [Unidentified]
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-02)
    - Negatives (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box 60)
    - Negatives (Box 61)
    - Negatives (Box 67)
    - Negatives (Box FB043)
    - Negatives (Box FB063)
    - Negatives (Box FB064)
    - Negatives (Box FB065)
    - Negatives (Box FB066)
    - Negatives (Box FB142)
    - Negatives (Box FB143)
    - Negatives (Box FB144)
    - Negatives (Box FB145)
    - Negatives (Box FB163)
    - Negatives (Box FB183)
    - Negatives (Box FB184)
    - Negatives (Box FB185)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
- Photographs
  Items in the shelf list marked with an asterisk (*) are mounted on a rejected print back to back.
  Many of the photographs listed below also exist as prints (see Negatives and proof prints above).
  - Character studies
    - The Abyssinian Jew (Oversize 1)
    - Alida's Hand *, 1943 (Oversize 1)
    - A Baby, 1924 (Oversize 1)
    - The Blacksmith (Oversize 1)
    - Boy Against Mantle *, 1930 (Oversize 1)
    - Carola, 1932 (Oversize 1)
    - Dancer, Liberia (Oversize 1)
      See also Son of a Liberian King.
    - Kathy (Oversize 1)
    - Korean Dancer (Oversize 1)
    - Koto Player, Kabuki Theatre (Japanese) (Oversize 1)
    - The Last of the Guslars, Yugoslavia (Story Teller of Yugoslavia), 1926 (Oversize 1)
    - Late in the Day, 1921 (Oversize 1)
    - Little Boy in Georgia, 1934 (Oversize 1)
    - Mother & Child, Arlington, Vt., 1958 (Oversize 1)
    - Mother and Children, 1955 (Oversize 1)
    - Mother & Daughter, 1945 (Oversize 2)
    - Nina and her Grandfather, 1931 (Oversize 2)
    - Nina at 2 years *, 1929 (Oversize 2)
    - Nina at 7, Reading on Porch *, 1934 (Oversize 2)
    - Nina at 12 * (Oversize 2)
    - Nude, carbon print, an early picture (Oversize 2)
    - Peter, 1959 (Oversize 2)
    - Quaker Ladies (Oversize 2)
    - Quaker Type, 1929 (Oversize 2)